Finding Aid for Hospitals (University of Michigan) records, 1875-2005
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Hospital Administration
  - Forsyth, John
    - Medical School
      - Department of Physiology (Box 119)
      - Department of Post-Graduate Medicine and Health Professions Education (Box 119)
      - Finances (Box 119)
      - General (Box 119)
      - Interim Medical School Facilities Study (Box 119)
      - Medical Science Research Building III (Box 119)
    - Medical Service Plan (Box 119)
    - Medical Staff Organization (Box 119)
    - Medicare/Medicaid (Box 119)
    - MedSport Program 1990 (Box 119)
    - Mergers (Box 120)
      - Mission Health Corporation, Daughters of Charity, Mercy Health Services
        - Advisory Committee 1995 (Box 120)
        - Anti-Trust Issues 1995 (Box 120)
        - Confidentiality Statement 1995 (Box 120)
        - Correspondence
          - Catherine McAuley Health Center 1991-1994 (Box 120)
          - Daughters of Charity National Health System 1995 (Box 120)
          - Mercy Health Services 1995-1997 (Box 120)
          - Mission Health Corporation 1995 (Box 120)
        - Disclosure List 1995 (Box 120)
        - Memorandum of Understanding 1995 (Box 120)
        - Miscellaneous 1994-1995 (Box 120)
        - Operational Integration Task Force 1995 (Box 120)
        - Oversight Committee 1995 (Box 120)
    - Michigan, State of (Box 121)
      - Correspondence -- General 1985-1989 (Box 121)
      - Department of Management and Budget (Box 121)
      - Department of Public Health
        - Bureau of Health Facilities 1986-1990 (Box 121)
        - Certificate of Need 1990 (Box 121)
        - Correspondence 1983-1989 (Box 121)
        - Correspondence 1990 (Box 122)
        - Letters of Agreement 1987 (Box 122)
        - Letters of Intent 1987-1989 (Box 122)
        - Licensing 1987-1990 (Box 122)
        - Meetings with Officers 1984-1986 (Box 122)
      - Department of Social Services (Box 122)
    - Michigan Council for Maternal and Child Health Care (Box 122)
    - Michigan Health Benefits Network 1990 (Box 122)
    - Michigan Health Council 1985-1986 (Box 122)
    - Michigan Health Data Corporation 1988-1989 (Box 122)
    - Michigan Health Systems 1985 (Box 122)
    - Michigan Hospital Association
      - Board Meeting Materials 1988-1989 (Box 122)
      - Board Meeting Materials 1990 (Box 123)
      - Committee on Teaching Hospitals 1981-1984 (Box 123)
      - Correspondence 1984-1990 (Box 123)
      - Medicaid 1988-1989 (Box 123)
      - Southeast Michigan Hospital Council 1983-1988 (Box 123)
    - Michigan Peer Review Organization (MPRO) 1983-1990 (Box 123)
    - Mission and Role Statement 1977-1987 (Box 124)
    - Organizational Structure 1989 (Box 124)
    - People's Community Hospital Authority/Association
      - Correspondence 1987-1989 (Box 124)
      - Strategic Plan 1986-1990 (Box 124)
      - Study 1987 (Box 124)
    - Public Advisory Board 1985 (Box 124)
    - Replacement Hospital Project (RHP)
      - Activation 1983-1985 (Box 124)
      - Activation 1986 (Box 125)
      - Audit 1984 (Box 125)
      - Bond Issue 1982-1986, 1990 (Box 125)
      - Capital Campaign 1983-1985 (Box 125)
      - Certificate of Need 1984 (Box 125)
      - Communications System Planning 1983 (Box 125)
      - Correspondence 1983-1987 (Box 125)
      - Dedication (Box 125)
      - Equipment Disposal 1983-1986 (Box 125)
      - Facility Naming 1982-1985 (Box 125)
      - Facilities Planning 1984-1985 (Box 125)
      - Gifts 1986 (Box 125)
    - Research Funding 1990 (Box 125)
    - Retreats 1984-1985 (June) (Box 125)
    - Retreats 1985 (July) -- 1990, 1992-1994 (Box 126)
    - Satellite Clinics
      - Brighton Health Center 1980-1988 (Box 126)
    - Security 1987 (Box 127)
    - School of Nursing (Box 127)
    - School of Public Health 1990 (Box 127)
    - Strategic Planning (includes site visits to peer medical institutions) 1982-1990, 1993-1998 (Box 127)
    - Surveys (Box 127)
    - Survival Flight 1982 (Box 127)
    - Survival Flight 1983-1990 (Box 128)
    - Taubman, A. Alfred (Taubman Library and Dance Column Sculpture) 1986 (Box 128)
    - Tax Equity and Fiscal Responsibility Act (TEFRA) 1983-1987 (Box 128)
    - Teaching and Administration Costs 1977-1985 (Box 128)
    - Uncompensated Care (Box 128)
    - United Health Systems 1987-1989 (Box 128)
    - United States
      - Government Accounting Office-Survey of Hospitals-Community Service Activity (Box 128)
      - Health and Human Services
        - General (Box 128)
        - Health Care Financing Administration 1987-1989 (Box 128)
    - University Hospitals Consortium
      - General 1983-1987 (Box 128)
      - General 1988-1990 (Box 129)
      - Executive Council 1988-1990 (Box 129)
    - University of Iowa Hospitals 1987 (Box 129)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital 1982-1988 (Box 129)
    - Vision 2000 (Box 129)
    - Visiting Nurse Association/Corporation 1985-1990 (Box 129)
    - Voluntary Hospitals of America 1985-1987 (Box 129)
    - Volunteer Recognition Week 1988 (Box 129)
    - Wayfinding 1987-1988 (Box 129)
    - Wayne County Executive Office 1984-1986 (Box 129)
    - Wayne County General Hospital 1980-1985 (Box 129)
    - Westland Medical Center 1984-1987 (Box 129)
  - Haynes, Harley
    - Correspondence (Box 10)
      - Administrative Staff (Box 10)
      - Alexander, John (Thoracic Surgery) (Box 10)
      - American College of Hospital Administrators (Box 10)
      - American College of Surgeons (Box 10)
      - American Hospital Association (Box 10)
      - American Medical Association (Box 10)
      - Anesthesia (Box 10)
      - Appreciation letters (Box 10)
      - Armed Services (World War II) (Box 10)
      - Attorney General and Auditor General (Box 10)
      - Badgley, Carl (Box 10)
      - Blood Bank (Box 10)
      - Building Program (Box 10)
      - Cancer (Box 10)
      - Chamber of Commerce (Box 10)
      - Christensen, John C. (Box 10)
      - Civilian Defense (Box 10)
      - Coller, Frederick A. (Box 11)
      - Committee on Office Personnel (Box 11)
      - Cook, A.B. (Box 11)
      - D.L. and R.C. Register (Box 11)
      - Delinquency Law (Box 11)
      - Department of Pediatrics and Infectious Diseases (Box 11)
      - Dietetics (Box 11)
      - Executive Committee (Box 11)
      - Executive Faculty (Box 11)
      - Executive Staff (Box 11)
      - Fever Therapy (Box 11)
      - Fire Protection (Box 11)
      - Fralick, Bruce (Box 11)
      - Food Poisoning Outbreak 1934 (Box 11)
      - Full and Part-time Departments (Box 11)
        (gross earnings)
      - Furstenberg, Albert C. (Box 11)
      - Greve, Robert (Box 11)
      - Haynes, Harley A. (Box 11)
      - Heads of Departments (Box 11)
        (communications)
      - Health Science Division (Box 11)
      - Historical Data (Box 11)
        (Reuben Peterson)
      - Hodges, Fred J. (Box 11)
      - Hospital Personnel Committee (Box 11)
      - Hospital Schools for Crippled Children (Box 11)
      - Infantile Paralysis (Box 11)
      - Insurance (Box 11)
      - Judges (Box 11)
        (probate court)
      - Kahn, Reuben L. (Box 11)
      - Ketcham, Dorothy (Box 11)
        (Social Services Department)
      - Labor (Box 11)
      - Legislators (Box 12)
      - Medical Records (Box 12)
      - Medical Statistics (Box 12)
      - Michigan Child Guidance Institute (Box 12)
      - Michigan Children's Aid Society (Box 12)
      - Michigan Crippled Children Commission (Box 12)
      - Michigan Department of Health (Box 12)
      - Michigan Hospital Association (Box 12)
      - Michigan Medical Service (Box 12)
      - Michigan State Board of Registration in Medicine (Box 12)
      - Miller, Norman (Box 12)
      - Music School (Box 12)
      - Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 12)
      - Northern Michigan Children's Clinic (Box 12)
      - Nursing Department (Box 12)
      - Part-time Physicians (Box 13)
      - Pharmacy (Box 13)
      - Pool and Physical Therapy (Box 13)
      - Recommendations to the Board of Regents (Box 13)
      - Ruthven, Alexander (University of Michigan President) (Box 13)
      - Smith, Shirley W. (Box 13)
      - Social Service Reports (Box 13)
      - Staff Lists (Box 13)
      - Statistical Survey of Services (Box 13)
      - Sullivan, Arthur (Box 13)
      - Theological Students (Box 13)
      - Tuberculosis Unit (Box 13)
      - Volunteer Nurse's Aides (Box 13)
  - Howe, Arlene
    - Bed Allocation System, Proposal for 1977 (Box 35)
    - Beaumont Hospital Visit 1978 (Box 35)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield (Box 35)
      (see Greater Detroit Area Hospital Council)
    - Comprehensive Health Planning Council of Southeastern Michigan (CHPC-SEM)
      (mostly materials re: Commission on Reduction of Excess Hospital Capacity)
      - 1979, 7 folders (Box 35)
      - 1980 (Box 35)
      - 1981 (Box 35)
    - Construction Account 1972-1974 (Box 35)
    - Cooperative and Shared Services 1979 (Box 35)
    - Director's Advisory Council 1980 (Box 35)
    - Discharge Planning 1977 (Box 35)
    - Greater Detroit Area Hospital Council (GDAHC)
      - 1973 (Box 35)
        (mostly about certificate of need)
      - 1977 (Box 35)
      - 1978 (folder 1) (Box 35)
        (includes Hospital Profile/Over-bedding Study materials from 1976)
      - 1978 (folder 2) (Box 36)
    - Hospital Planning Council 1976 (Box 36)
    - Long Range Planning 1973 (Box 36)
    - Major Areas of Responsibility: Associate and Assistant Director 1972-1973 (Box 36)
    - Medical Center Planning 1969-1970 (Box 36)
    - Medical Education, University Hospital 1977 (Box 36)
    - Michigan State Plan for the Construction of Hospital and Medical Facilities 1977 (Box 36)
    - Mott, C.S., Planning Committee 1962-1965, 3 folders (Box 36)
      (mostly 1964 and 1965 materials)
    - New Hospital Committee 1966-1967 (Box 36)
    - Planning, Miscellaneous 1969-1974 (Box 36)
    - Remodeling and Renovation (Box 37)
      - 1970 (Box 37)
      - 1972-1973 (Box 37)
      - 1974 (Box 37)
        (includes earlier and later materials)
      - 1975, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Repair Maintenance and Alterations 1973-1974, 2 folders (Box 37)
    - Space Utilization Committee 1971, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - University Hospitals Executive Board
    - Executives Council Papers 1932-1944 (Box 14)
      (national organization for directors of university hospitals)
    - Executives Council Papers 1932-1944 (Box 15)
      (national organization for directors of university hospitals, continued)
    - Executives Council Papers 1932-1944 (Box 16)
    - Executive Staff Minutes (Box 27)
      - December 1919-June 1930 (Box 27)
      - October 1930-June 1940 (Box 27)
    - Board in Control Minutes 1945-1972 (Box 27)
      (continued in box 51)
    - Board in Control Supporting Materials December 1969-September 1972, 3 volumes (Box 50)
    - Board in Control Minutes September 1972-June 1974, 3 volumes (Box 50)
      (continues as University Hospital Executive Board)
    - Executive Board Minutes (Box 51)
      - September 1974-August 1976, 4 volumes (Box 51)
      - September 1976-February 1978 (includes "Executive Directory", 6 volumes (Box 52)
      - April 1978-January 1979, 5 volumes (Box 53)
      - January 1979-January 1980, 5 volumes (Box 54)
      - January 1980-April 1981, 5 volumes (Box 55)
      - April 1981-July 1982, 5 volumes (Box 56)
      - October 1982-October 1983, 6 volumes (Box 57)
      - November 1983-March 1986, 10 folders; 5 volumes (Box 58)
      - April 1986-July 1988, 21 folders (Box 59)
      - October 1988-March 1991, 21 folders (Box 79)
      - April 1991-March 1994, 21 folders (Box 80)
      - April 1994-December 1996, 19 volumes (Box 81)
  - Warren, Larry
    - Correspondence 1996-2000, 10 volumes (Box 130)
      [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2028 ]
    - Correspondence 2001-2005, 10 volumes (Box 131)
    - Director's Forum 1996-2004 Zugich, John, 39 video tapes (Box 132)
  - Zugich, John
    - Ambulatory Planning (Box 19)
    - Attitude Survey (Box 19)
      (University Hospital ex-patient telephone interview)
    - Bed Need Methodology (Box 19)
    - Biomedical Research (Box 19)
    - Blue Cross/Blue Shield: Over-bedding issue (Box 19)
    - Bond Financing (Box 19)
    - Capital Financing (Box 19)
    - Certificate of Need
      - Application Procedure (Box 19)
      - Comments (Box 19)
      - Rules (Box 19)
    - Clinical Faculty Office Space Survey (Box 19)
    - Clippings
      - 1975-1976 (Box 19)
      - 1977-1978 (Box 19)
    - Departmental Program Survey (Box 19)
    - Emergency and Unscheduled Patient Care Unit (Box 19)
      (report on the development of a responsive unit)
    - Fund raising: Feasibility study on private funds/sources (Box 19)
    - Galens and Gift Shop (Box 19)
    - Health Facilities Construction Costs (Box 19)
    - Hospital Planning Committee: Bed Need Methodology Subcommittee (Box 19)
    - Hospital Planning Objectives (Box 19)
    - House Officer Training Program Study (Box 19)
    - Management Committee Structure (Box 19)
    - Mission and Role Statement (Box 19)
    - National Health Planning and Resources Development Act (Box 19)
    - Obstetric Bed Utilization (Box 19)
    - Patient Augmentation (Box 19)
      (patients referred by the Department of Mental Health and Department of Corrections)
    - Patient Origin, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Patient Statistics (Box 19)
      (miscellaneous)
    - Plans (Box 19)
      (miscellaneous assumptions, short-term plans, long-term plans)
    - Quality Assurance Program (Box 20)
    - Renovation and Replacement
      - General, 6 folders (Box 20)
      - Administrative Services Building (Box 20)
      - Anesthesia (Box 20)
      - Animal Research (Box 20)
      - Bed Plan Data (Box 20)
      - Bed Quotas (Box 20)
      - Blood Bank (Box 20)
      - Burn Unit (Box 20)
      - Cardiac Study Unit (Box 20)
      - Children's Psychiatric Unit (Box 20)
      - Clinical Laboratories (Box 20)
      - Coagulation Laboratories (Box 20)
      - Data Systems (Box 20)
      - Dietetics (Box 21)
      - Emergency Room Equipment Fund (Box 21)
      - Feasibility Study (Box 21)
      - Health Maintenance Organization (Box 21)
        (North Outpatient Building)
      - Heart Station (Box 21)
      - Hospital Planning Committee
        - 1975 (Box 21)
        - 1976, 3 folders (Box 21)
        - 1977 (Box 21)
      - Information and Communication System (Box 21)
      - Inpatient Bed Care Units (Box 21)
      - Inpatient Care Unit Task Force (Box 21)
      - Inpatient Modernization: 10, 11, 12 levels (Box 21)
      - Laboratories (Box 21)
      - Long Range Plans, 2 folders (Box 21)
      - Medical Center Library (Box 21)
        (request for HEW grant)
      - Medical Records (Box 22)
      - Mott: Intensive Care (Box 22)
      - Nuclear Medicine (Box 22)
      - Nuclear Pharmacy (Box 22)
      - Neuropsychiatric Institute (Box 22)
      - Operating Rooms (Box 22)
      - Outpatient Program (Box 22)
      - Paging-Fire Alarm System (Box 22)
      - Parkview Building (Box 22)
      - Patient Care Planning Task Force (Box 22)
      - Personnel (Box 22)
      - Phase I
        - Components: Appendices (Box 22)
        - Construction Timetables (Box 22)
        - Functional Planning, 3 folders (Box 22)
        - Fund Raising (Box 22)
        - HEW Grant Request, 4 folders (Box 22)
        - Organizational charts and staffing projects (Box 22)
        - Prospective (Box 22)
      - Phase IA: Options (Box 22)
      - Phased Replacement vs. One-time Replacement (Box 22)
      - Planned Policy Group (Box 23)
      - Planned Process and Background Information (Box 23)
      - Plant Fund (Box 23)
      - Policy and Program (Box 23)
      - Purchasing Offices (Box 23)
      - Radiology
        - General (Box 23)
        - E.M.I. Scanner (Box 23)
        - Linear Accelerator (Box 23)
        - Simulator (Box 23)
        - Ultrasonic (Box 23)
      - Renal (Box 23)
      - Re-use Study (Box 23)
      - Simpson Memorial Institute (Box 23)
      - Site Options/Locations (Box 23)
      - Status Reports (Box 23)
      - Terraces (Box 23)
      - Total Replacement (Box 23)
      - University Architects Service (Box 23)
      - Utilities (Box 23)
      - 2nd Level Fire Stairs (Box 23)
      - 4th-7th Stairway (Box 23)
      - 5th Level Lobby (Box 23)
      - 6th Floor Administrative Wing (Box 23)
      - 6E-6W (Box 23)
      - 7th Level (Box 23)
      - 8th, 9th, 10th Floors (Box 23)
      - 9E-9W (Box 23)
      - 10E-11E-12N (Box 23)
      - 11W (Box 23)
      - 13th Level (Box 23)
    - Space Allocation (Box 23)
    - Surveys (includes patient information surveys), 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Task Groups (Box 23)
    - University of Michigan Functional and Resource Analysis (UMFRA) (Box 23)
    - Zugich, John (Box 23)
      (retirement clipping)
- Nursing
  The Nursing series (32 linear feet) contains information on the various nursing programs provided by the Hospitals, as well as nursing administrators. Many of these records document the various programs made available to assist and educate nurses, and the administrators that have helped implement them. The series contains various nursing meeting minutes, director correspondence, and nursing program manuals.
  The Associate Director for Nursing subseries (5 linear feet) is made up of records from the nursing administrators; Ann Vose, Marjorie Jackson, Sally Sample, and Sue McMahon. Administrative council meeting minutes and topical files make up a bulk of the subseries. Much of this subseries also consists of minutes and projects relating to the various nursing committees. The series is arranged by the creator of the records which includes Sue McMahon, Sally Sample, and Ann Vose (along with Marjorie Jackson and Sally Sample).
  The Clinical Nursing Specialist Program subseries (1 linear foot) consist of a small number of records relating to the development of this program. The subseries also contain papers presented at clinical nursing symposiums as well as information about mental health nurses and nursing shortages.
  The Educational Services for Nursing subseries (6 linear feet) contains records documenting the educational programs and projects for nurses. Included within the subseries are the pamphlets, videotapes, and the educational conferences used to help educate nurses and nursing students within the University of Michigan. A large number of binders are contained within this subseries and include orientation manuals, program manuals, and project overviews. This subseries also contains a number of newsletters sent out by educational services department, and policies for units within the Educational Services for Nursing group. This subseries is arranged alphabetically and covers the years 1978 to 1995.
  The Nursing Administration subseries (5 linear feet) contains records from the committees, and decisions made by the administration as a whole. This includes minutes from committee meetings from the administrative meetings, as well as the Continuing Care Committee. Goals and objectives are contained within the subseries and help document some of the projects and decisions that have been implemented by the administration.
  The Nursing Services subseries (1 linear foot) consists of meeting minutes, reports from staff members, various policy manuals, as well as some photographs. This subseries is arranged alphabetically and contains materials from 1969 to 1986. The subseries contains materials relating to nursing needs, nursing committees, search for project directors, and many other tasks relating to the services offered to University of Michigan nurses.
  - Associate Director for Nursing
    - McMahon, Sue
      - Committees
        - Committee Member Lists 1982 (Box 146)
          [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2034 ]
        - Committees 1992 (Box 146)
        - Hospital Data Systems Advisory Committee 1975, 3 folders (Box 146)
        - Information Services Advisory Committee 1985 (Box 146)
        - Nursing Computer Planning Committee 1976-1978, 2 folders (Box 146)
        - Nursing Information Communication Committee 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 146)
        - Nursing Information Communication Committee 1983, 2 folders (Box 146)
        - Nursing Information Systems Coordinating Committee 1977-1991, 3 folders (Box 146)
        - Nursing Information Systems Coordinating Committee: Patient Care Documentation 1991 (Box 146)
        - Nursing Planning Committee Orientation Packet 1981 (Box 146)
        - Nursing Research Review and Study Committee 1982 (Box 146)
        - Planning Committee 1976-1979, 2 folders (Box 147)
        - Planning Committee Orientation Packet 1981 (Box 147)
      - Nurse Employment
        - Activity and Workload Index Graphs 1983-1984 (Box 147)
        - Career Transition Center 1991 (Box 147)
        - Computer Scheduling 1974-1976 (Box 147)
        - Contract Negotiations 2000-2001 (Box 147)
        - Duke Site Visit 1978 (Box 147)
        - Employment-Related Correspondence 1992 (Box 147)
        - Huron Valley Visiting Nurses Positions 1996 (Box 147)
        - Labor Distribution Report 1985-1986 (Box 147)
        - Medical Head Nurse M.A.R. Drafts 1973 (Box 147)
        - Medical Head Nurse Meeting Minutes 1971-1975 (Box 147)
        - Nurse Aide Cyclical Schedules 1971 (Box 147)
        - Nurse Aides Handbook 1966 (Box 147)
        - Nurse Employment Graphs 1951-1971 (Box 147)
        - Nurse Staffing Role Task Comparison 1980 (Box 147)
        - Nurse Staffing Systems: New Approaches (Box 147)
        - Nursing 4B 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 147)
        - Nursing 6A 1996, 2 folders (Box 147)
        - Nursing Services 1972 (Box 148)
        - Nursing Shortage 1969-1970 (Box 148)
        - Nursing Staffing Data 1983 (Box 148)
        - Nursing Trend Data 1983-1984 (Box 148)
        - Psychiatric Nursing Position Control Roster 1988 (Box 148)
        - Reorganization of Nursing Resources in Hospitals (Box 148)
        - Research Position Interview Schedule (Box 148)
        - RN and LPN Orientation Booklet 1992 (Box 148)
        - RN Employment Statistics 1987 (Box 148)
        - Service Unit Description 1972 (Box 148)
        - Standards of Nursing Practice 1973 (Box 148)
        - Statement of Work 1977 (Box 148)
        - Thomas Jefferson Hospital Site Visit 1979 (Box 148)
        - UM Professional Nurse Council Agreement 1976, 1978, 1984, 1987, 1992, 1997, 2001, 3 folders (Box 148)
        - Work Stoppage 1977, 1981, 1988-1989, 2 folders (Box 148)
      - Patient Care
        - Child Care Center (Box 148)
        - Clinical Service Locations 1984-1985 (Box 148)
        - Inpatient Census System 1982 (Box 148)
        - Maternal and Child Health Care Center Operational Narrative 1987 (Box 148)
        - Patient Activity Budgets 1984-1986 (Box 148)
        - Patient Activity Budgets 1986-1987 (Box 148)
        - Patient Activity Budgets 1988-1991 (Box 148)
        - Patient Activity Report-Finance 1987-1988 (Box 148)
        - Patient Care System Implementation 1992 (Box 148)
        - Patient Video Monitoring System 1988 (Box 148)
        - Patient Move Day
          - Bed Utilization and Availability 1985 (Box 149)
          - Budget 1985 (Box 149)
          - Care Continuity 1985 (Box 149)
          - Diagrams 1985 (Box 149)
          - Logistics Task Force 1985 (Box 149)
          - Manual 1985 (Box 149)
          - Memorandum of Understanding 1986 (Box 149)
          - News Bulletin 1985 (Box 149)
          - Outpatient Operations 1985 (Box 149)
          - Outstanding Issues 1985 (Box 149)
          - Patient Move Task Force 1984-1985, 5 folders (Box 149)
          - Patient Profile Report 1985 (Box 149)
          - Policies 1985 (Box 149)
          - Sequence and Narrative 1985 (Box 149)
          - Staff Meeting Notes 1985 (Box 149)
          - Turnover Dates 1985 (Box 149)
      - Projects and Programs